(Mrs Hofstadter:)Sheldon.
(Sheldon:)You tracked my phone?
(Howard:)Yeah.
(Sheldon:)Boy, you chase one balloon
for three miles.
(Penny:)We were worried about you.
(Sheldon:)Don't be melodramatic.
(Sheldon:)I'm just getting on a train
and leaving forever.
(Leonard:)Seriously? You don't even have
a change of clothes or a toothbrush.
(Sheldon:)My plan is to stop
at malls and buy what I need.
(Sheldon:)It's called living off the land.
(Leonard:)Okay, I know you're upset
and there's a lot of stuff going on,
(Leonard:)but it's nothing we can't work out.
Come on, let's get you home.
(Sheldon:)No. I've reached my breaking point.
I need to leave. Now.
(Penny:)-And go where?
-It doesn't matter.
(Leonard:)So a few things don't go your way,
(Leonard:)and your best decision
is to ride the rails like a hobo?
(Sheldon:)I suppose it is.
(Sheldon:)Except I have a credit card.
(Sheldon:)And I refuse to carry
my laptop at the end of a stick.